I have to ask a question here is not
snitching still a thing in the black
community I I thought we got over that
like Jerry curls and black Bart Simpson
t-shirts okay for any snitching novices
out there stop snitching was a movement
uh to try and convince black people to
not talk to the police uh which raises
the question somebody really needed to
organize
that now as misguided as the stop
snitching campaign is it was definitely
a thing that caught on in the earlys and
the guy who organized it was this guy
skinny
Suge not to be confused with fullsize
Suge who as I said before was accused of
running over CLE bone
Sloan
allegedly even though it's on camera and
everybody saw
it y bone I just snitched for you man I
did that for
you did it helping a brother out he
helping a brother out okay anyway skinny
Shug I can't believe that his
name skinny Suge was a guy from
Baltimore who made a series of stop
snitching DVDs in which he said things
like this snitching I hate all you
so I need y volun y
information on who these is man so I can
let the whole mother World
know not on par with the I Have a Dream
speech
but in his defense actually there is no
defense now since then skinny Suge and
even the guy who shot that video wound
up in jail I don't know if they were
snitched on or not but I get why that
would be their cause now of course now
snitching isn't just limited to Black
Culture everybody has a snitch code
right just ask Robert dairo never ride
on your
friends and always keep your mouth
shut yeah see this Code of Silence works
for both gangster and
Gangstar